Hey!
Straw Hat Luffy, you're out!
What?
It's over!
Straw Hat Luffy has eeped his way to defeat
as Team Foxy claims victory in the first round!
Showdown on the cliff, red light, green light.
The Foxy Pirates have claimed the victory for round one
in the rematch of the Davy Mac fight.
It's time for the boss to claim his prize.
Which member of the Straw Hat crew will he choose?
The one I want is.
Oh, it's so obvious, isn't it, boss?
You! The archaeologist Nicarabind!
You want me?
Oh!
Oh, the boss has decided that his pick
for this round is Nico Robin!
Oh, Captain, you're such a naughty boy.
Why, boss?
Why didn't you get my adorable little choppy back?
We can't afford to leave that woman on the Straw Hat's team.
She's far too dangerous.
Bringing her to our side will give us the advantage
from here on out.
But...
This way, taking Dr. Chopper back in the next round
will be a piece of cake.
Now I get it.
You're so smart, boss.
Faith, it's the best.
Oh, I get it.
You're so smart, boss.
Faith, it's the best.
Robin!
Robin, my love!
See you later.
I feel her pain.
She's trying to hide her sorrow
behind that beautiful smile.
She hates being apart from me.
How dare they take my sweet ramen away?
Even if it's the rules, do they know nothing of love?
Robin!
So, how does it look?
Splendid.
Perfect, it complements that beautiful hair.
You were the one we wanted from the beginning.
Aw, she's so popular.
She, uh...
She seems to be getting along with them pretty well.
It figures.
I never trusted that woman to begin with.
What are you talking about?
Robin trusts us to get her back.
That's all, I think.
As always, Nami's right on the money.
I'm gonna give it everything I've got in the next round
and help win Robin back for us.
Let's get this next round going!
Let me at him!
Luffy, you can't compete in the next round.
You're in the third round, remember?
Geez, just remember the rules already.
All right, guess I'm on cheering duty then.
With Robin gone, that means there are only five of us
in the next event.
Stupid straw hats.
You've lost more than a member of your crew.
You've lost a major part of your offense.
How do you like them grapes?
Or apples, whatever.
On to the next event.
Fell, fell, fell, fell, fell, fell, fell, fell, fell.
Round two will be held on the long reef.
The game will be Dash Touch Domination or DTD for short.
Although this is a six on six group competition,
the absence of Nico Robin forces the Straw Hats
the Straw Hats to compete with only five players.
The rules are simple, basically it's played the same way
as the game Red Light, Green Light.
Whoever moves even just the tiniest little bit
after the light stops calling is out.
Whichever team touches the stoplight at the top
of the reef first will be declared the winner.
But this is no kid's game.
Remember, when pirates play Red Light, Green Light,
they play hard and they play to win.
The use of weapons is approved and encouraged.
This is what makes DTT a truly perilous game.
Playing for the Straw Hat team is,
the same boring lineup as always.
Shut it, jerk!
Leading off for Team Foxy is our beloved idol,
Parcha, and the beastly oddity, Hamburr.
Soon I will have Little Choppy right back in my hand.
Boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop, boop.
The rest of the team consists of the
Everswift Chicky Cheetah, the Fishman Capote,
and back for some vengeance for their loss in the groggy ring,
we have Tackle Machine Pickles and Big Panda Wotan.
We're gonna make those Straw Hat losers pay
for humiliating us.
These six competitors will make Team Foxy
a force to be reckoned with.
Hey, why's the old Stiltzke
up there, riding around with him?
And last but not least, the role of our stoplight
will be played by none other than the nomad himself Kamsiek.
This great fool, I mean man of bravery,
stood atop Stiltz for ten years to touch the heavens.
This makes him the logical choice to stand
at the top of the reef and be it!
I'm seriously sick and tired of high places, though.
Hey, wait a minute. If the old man is the stoplight, that gives us a big advantage in the DTD.
Uh, let's not get ahead of ourselves here.
But who stops right, you guys? This could be just the lucky break that we meet.
You sure about all this, Captain?
Come on, this is nothing! If our crew is strong enough to battle the treacherous wide open sea, then this is child's play! Don't sweat this small stuff!
You said it, boss!
Yeah, our captain's the greatest!
Child's play, huh? Then why did you give us this unfair, docked-up course giving you the advantage from the start?
I guess using that dodo beam really is his only talent.
Stupid fox!
Split head!
Hey, dodo beam! I'm the stupid fox! Split head!
Boss, no!
Listen to them!
You certainly wear your heart on your sleeve, Captain Foxy.
To kick off this event as the DTD rules state, both teams must start by calling out the first step!
Taking the first step, now!
So it begins! And Captain Foxy is already off to an early lead!
It's because of those huge freaks.
If we follow the boss's plan, this'll be easy! Let's do it!
Yeah!
I'm sure this goes without saying, but there's more to winning this thing than just being the first one to touch the stoplight.
This twisted terrain makes it easy to lose your balance when coming to a sudden stop, so that'll be the most likely time for the enemy to attack.
Hey, split head! If you screw around with this race, I'm gonna have something to say about it!
Split head?
Like I'd even need to interfere! We could win this race in our sleeves, straw hat!
Stoplight! Are you ready to begin?
Uh-huh!
Then take your position!
Yeah!
To recap, Team Foxy claimed the victory in the last round!
Let's see what happens in round two, DTD!
Ready, go!
Green!
Run! Quick, Hamburg!
Cheeky Cheetah sprints ahead to take an early lead with Full Dash Hamburg following behind in second place!
Meanwhile, on the straw hat side, Zoro and Zanji are out in front running neck and neck!
Move! You're in the way!
No, you move! You're in my way!
How can those two idiots run and argue at the same time?
Hey! Knock it off, you two!
Yeah! Concentrate on the game!
They're amazing!
Night!
What the heck?!
How could you hold that word out for so long, freaky old stilts guy?!
He makes an ideal stoplight!
Red!
Let me die, loser!
What was that, fist-flake head?!
You hurt me!
The only ones to worry about from the straw hat team are those two!
Let's knock them out of the game quick, just like we planned!
This is it.
It can!
Spunk attack!
Oh, crap, it's headed right for him!
And the old man's about to finish his red light!
We don't have time to worry about that!
I...
This is it.
Quick, stop me!
If we move, we'll be out!
You're out.
An early upset on Team Foxy for Pickles and Big Fan!
They've been knocked off the course and out of the game!
All right, Zoro and Soji! Way to go! Nice one!
Whatever! It's no big deal!
We only need one person on Team Foxy to touch him for the win,
and it doesn't matter which one of them does it!
Perfect!
Chicky Cheetah, Port Cha, and Hamburg are out in front
and have quite a significant lead over the straw hats!
Oh, my! That put me in a weird totally-gonna-win mood!
Damn, they're way too fast!
It looks like Zoro and Sanji are our only hope!
Stupid moss head, sword swinger!
Delusional love cook!
I'm warning you, I'm on a very important mission
to rescue my sweet Robin.
If you do anything to get in the way,
I don't have time to listen to this crap!
Hey! Hold on! I wasn't finished, you jerk!
Despite losing two players,
Team Foxy has a huge lead
and is the closest to reaching the stoplight!
At this rate, the straw hats don't stand a chance
of winning this round!
Go! Go!
That's it, yes, just like that!
Keep it up and we'll win!
Team Foxy has a huge lead
Dammit, it's your fault we've fallen so far behind,
you stupid moss head!
If we lose this round, I'm...
How'd this happen?
The path is gone!
How in the hell can anyone get lost on a path like this one?
You can see the old man at the end of it!
Even your sense of direction can't be that bad!
I can make up some time if I use this as a shortcut.
It's risky, but it's do or die.
Looks like Sanji is taking a huge gamble!
Close one.
It seems that Sanji's big gamble has paid off!
Now he's right behind the lead group and closing in fast!
Not fair!
Hey, Berg, hurry!
He's gaining on us!
What?
What do you want?
In my opinion, it never hurts to reduce the number of opponents you have.
Time for the three of you to kick the button.
Oh, crap!
Nami, you stop!
What do we do?
We have no choice.
Everybody run for it!
Butcher!
Hey, get back here!
You can't escape from me!
Yeah!
Yee-yah!
Come here!
Now!
Man, the old stilts guy's green is even longer than it was last time.
He's sleeping?
Hey!
Wake up!
Don't be sleeping!
Green light, red light, stop!
Let's do it!
Ah!
Damn it!
You're out!
Ah!
Taken by surprise that the stoplight was napping!
Capote was caught off guard, unable to stop, and is out!
What kind of weirdo falls asleep standing up leaning against a rock like that?
That old stilts guy sure is something!
All right.
I'm within range now.
What the heck?
I thought this would be an easy win.
Now I'm starting to get worried.
Now the four frontrunners are all within 100 meters of the stoplight!
It's going to be a mad dash to the finish!
One of these four will most likely be our winner!
Which one will it be?
All right, Dodgy!
You can do it!
Nobody's paying any attention to us.
Yeah.
Completely ignored.
This definitely feels a bit useless, doesn't it?
Well, at least we can take comfort in knowing that we're not the only useless ones here.
The path ended again.
It's cold. I want to get this over with so I can go eat something warm.
Out of my way!
All right, Hamper! Let him have it!
This time, you're mine!
So, you want a piece of me, gorilla man?
Poop, poop, poop, poop!
You're mincemeat!
Hamper and Sanji are now going head to head!
Meanwhile, Chicky Cheetah is racing towards the stoplight!
So, by keeping him occupied, it seems that Sanji has fallen right into Porches' travel!
Oh no!
Victory is ours!
Damn it!
Chicky Cheetah is just a few leaps away from touching the stoplight!
You're out!
Huh?
What?!
He was sneezing!
Tongjin hasn't even started calling out red light green light yet!
He was just starting to sneeze!
All of that rotten speed was for nothing!
Chicky Cheetah had a false start and is now out!
Damn it!
Don't sneeze in the middle of the game stoplight!
I can't believe it!
We were so close to winning, too!
That crazy old stills guy, even his snot is long!
Phew, that was a close one.
He was sneezing?
Get a hold of yourself, Hamburg!
This is no laughing matter!
We've just got to win this thing so we can get my little choppy back!
Both teams are closing in on the stoplight!
And with only a short distance to go, the next play should determine the outcome of the game!
But which player will it be?
The Dua of Porchand Hamburg?
Or Sanji?
We'll find out soon!
The moment of truth is about to begin!
The stoplight is definitely calling out his line this time!
This is it!
Pardon me!
Pepper, come on!
What are you doing?
Robin's personal savior has arrived to save the day!
Sanji!
No way!
What happened to Porcha?
And now that I've brought Robin back to our crew, she'll definitely fall in love with me!
He's Sanji! Touch him! You gotta touch him to win the game!
All right, time to win this thing. Thanks for everything, old timer.
Samji has turned around and started running back down the trail before touching the stoplight!
What is he doing?!
Even if she's the enemy, I can't obey the lady in distress!
Incredible! The nefarious cook, Sanji, has saved our beloved Porcha!
Delight!
Hamburg is desperately trying to hold on while remaining still!
But Sanji is most likely going to be out of the game despite his valiant and heroic rescue of Porcha!
No, wait! There's Sanji! And he has Porcha!
Not only that, but he seems to be holding completely still despite his current situation!
He's out in the middle of the water, but he's not moving it in!
He's safe!
Impossible!
How can he be standing out there like that? There's no way he's touching the bottom!
Oh, I get it! He's treading water!
And he's doing it while carrying Porcha and keeping his upper body completely motionless!
He's just like a swan on a lake, kicking furiously beneath the surface while looking elegant and graceful above!
As long as the stoplight can't see him moving, he's undeniably safe!
Sanji is incredibly determined to win!
No matter what happens, I will save Robin!
Sanji still has a chance to touch the stoplight and claim the victory!
Captain!
You risked everything to save yourself!
Impressive, Mr. Cook!
Sanji, you're awesome!
Oh my, I could really fall for you, Mr. Cook!
No! Both Porcha and Sanji have dived underwater!
You two move, you're out!
Hey, what's your problem? Just keep swimming!
Do you want me to drown or something?
Oh, what have I done? Sweet Robin!
And with the stoplight's call, the game is once again underway!
The only competitors left in the round at this point are Hamburg of Team Foxy as well as...
We're almost to the stoplight!
There's nobody left to stop us!
I don't believe it! We're gonna be the first ones to touch him!
Come on, let's all touch him together!
Yeah!
Amazingly enough, the forgotten trio of Straw Hat Slowpokes are now poised to be the first ones to touch the stoplight!
What an amazing turn of events! Who would have even thought it possible?
Just when I finally get to the real path...
Find you in the middle of it!
Out of my way!
We did it!
This is it! The Straw Hats are about to win!
Yeah! We win!
Check!
Oh!
Hamburg is the first player to touch the stoplight!
Congratulations to Team Foxy!
The winner of Round Two's Dash Touch Domination Game!
That's two victories in a row!
We're gonna sweep you in this rematch!
Hmm. What happened? Is it over?
You're the one who ended it, you idiot!
And you totally ruined everything for us!
This is all your fault, Zorro!
That's all right. It doesn't matter. I'm up next.
The captain's gonna win his crew back, no problem!
Haven't you forgotten an important little fact-straw hat?
That was your second loss!
So in addition to Nico-Robin, you're about to lose one more member of your crew!
On top of that, you can only win back one crew member per event!
Therefore, even in the slimmest, most inconceivable, you're about to lose one member of your crew!
There's a probable chance that you win the next round!
Come on! Get to the point, Splithead!
Split?
What he's trying to say, Captain, is that there's only one more round remaining,
so even if you win it, you can only take back one person.
Huh?
So no matter what does or doesn't happen in the next round, the fact remains!
You've already lost one of your crewmates forever!
Fee-fee-fee-fee-fee!
Thats coming from my new guides,
that's the only one last episode!
i'll follow you still!
Yeah!
What you!
That looks stunning!
Impact!
What you mean!
How did you play?
How can I miss it??
Today?
How can I speak just today?
C'mon toéner!
Square off, the final combat round!
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!
Oh yeah!